Guide to the North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
1909-2011
1909 2011
North Carolina State University Student Media Authority
UA 016.035
The Student Media Authority Records contain budget and financial statements, contracts, correspondence, minutes, staff applications, layout and design information, and publications. There is also a large amount of photographic materials, including CDs, DVDs, photographic prints, negatives, contact sheets, and slides, most of which are from student photographers. The collection includes records of the Agromeck office from 1909 to 2011, the Technician office from 1939 to 2011, the WKNC Radio Station from 1922 to 2006, the Windhover from 1928 to 2011, the Nubian Message from 2007-2009, and a small number of records from other publications.
The Publications Board was formed at North Carolina State College in or before 1933 to oversee creation of student publications. By 1937, it included representatives from student publications such as the Agromeck, Technician, Wataugan, Southern Engineer, and Agriculturist. By the late 1940s, it also included representatives from the student radio station WVWP. In the following decades, the organization continued to oversee the finances and leadership of student publications at North Carolina State University. It underwent various name changes, becoming known as the Student Media Board by the mid-2000s. As of 2010, Student Media is part of the Division of Student Affairs and is based in Witherspoon Student Center. It includes 220 paid and volunteer student positions. Student Media publications include the Agromeck yearbook, Technician newspaper, Windhover literary magazine, and the Nubian Message, an African American student newspaper. Student Media also oversees the student radio station, WKNC, and student television station, Wolf TV.
21.45 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Collection is open for research; access requires at least 48 hours advance notice, with the exception that patrons may not access original CDs and DVDs to view files. Use copies must be produced prior to accessing records on digital media.
Transferred from North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs.
This collection is arranged in eight series: 1.Student Media Board Records2. Agromeck Records3. Technician Records4. WKNC Student Radio Station Records5. Windhover Records6. Other Student Publication Records 7. Photographs8. Negatives, contact sheets, and slides
The Student Media Authority oversees creation of campus student publications at North Carolina State University, which include a yearbook, a daily newspaper, literary magazine, and African American student newspaper. It also oversees the student radio station, WKNC, and student television station, Wolf TV.
The Publications Board was formed at North Carolina State College in or before 1933 to oversee creation of student publications. By 1937, it included representatives from student publications such as the Agromeck, Technician, Wataugan, Southern Engineer, and Agriculturist. By the late 1940s, it also included representatives from the student radio station WVWP. In the following decades, the organization continued to oversee the finances and leadership of student publications at NCSU. It underwent various name changes, becoming known as the Board of Student Publications around 1953, the Publications Authority in 1969, and the Publications Board in the early 1980s. By the mid 2000s the governing body became known as the Student Media Board.
In 2011, Student Media publications at North Carolina State University include the Agromeck yearbook, Technician newspaper, Windhover literary magazine, and the Nubian Message, an African American student newspaper. Student Media also oversees the student radio station, WKNC, and student television station, Wolf TV.
As of 2011, Student Media is part of the Division of Student Affairs and is based in Witherspoon Student Center. It includes 220 paid and volunteer student positions. WKNC broadcasts 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, while the Technician publishes daily and circulates around 10,000 print copies each day. The Agromeck, Technician and Windhover routinely receive national recognition as top student publications, and WKNC is consistently recognized as one of the top student radio stations in the Triangle.
1903 First edition of the Agromeck published.
1920 First issue of Technician published.
1958 The student radio station adopts the call letters WKNC.
1964 First edition of Windhover published.
1992 Nubian Message first published.
2010 Wolf TV becomes part of Student Media.
University Archives Photograph Collection, Organization Photographs, UA 023.023
North Carolina State University Division of Student Affairs Record Group, UA 016
The Student Media Authority Records contain budget and financial statements, contracts, correspondence, minutes, staff applications, layout and design information, and publications. There is also a large amount of photographic materials, including CDs, DVDs, photographic prints, negatives, contact sheets, and slides, most of which are from student photographers. The collection includes records of the Agromeck office from 1909 to 2011, the Technician office from 1939 to 2011, the WKNC Radio Station from 1922 to 2006, the Windhover from 1928 to 2011, the Nubian Message from 2007-2009, and a small number of records from other publications.
North Carolina State University Student Media Authority; North Carolina State University--Students--History; North Carolina State University Student Media Authority; College sports Photography; Universities and colleges North Carolina Student activities; North Carolina College radio stations; North Carolina College students Social life and customs; North Carolina Student publications
- Student Media Board Records, 1928-2008; 1928 2008
  This series contains the records of the Student Media Board, the governing body for student publications and student media productions at NCSU. It has previously been known as the Publications Boards, the Board of Student Publications, and the Publications Authority. The majority of the documents are meeting minutes and financial records. Also included are publication contracts, reports, manuals, applications for editorships, promotional materials, and other administrative information.
  - Awards, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Banquet Programs, 1937-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Banquet Programs, 1949-1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Student Publications Functions and Policies, 1960-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1951, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Budgets and Finances, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Constitution and By-laws of Board of Student Publications, 1954-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and Budget Information (1 of 2), 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Budget Information (2 of 2), 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Resolutions, and 1958-1959 Annual Report, 1946-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - General Records, 1964-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - General Records, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - General Records, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - General Records, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Go Pack! poster, 2003 (Oversizeflatbox 43)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Print Shop Correspondence and Contracts, 1951-1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Materials, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Materials, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials and Reports, 1928-1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for Student Fee Adjustment, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Publications and Student Body Statutes, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Report on College and University Campus Student Press, 1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Selection of Station Managers and Editors, 1970-1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Student Government Correspondence, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Student Media Annual Report, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Student Media Manuals and Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student Publications Newsclippings, 1958-1968, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Technician Newsclippings, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Wolfpack Club Print Contract, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Wolfpack Club Print Contract- Technician Newsclippings, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Agromeck Records, 1909-2010; 1909 2010
  This series contains records from the Agromeck, NCSU's yearbook. It contains digital production files, contracts, staff applications, photographs, and publications.
  - Agromeck, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Agromeck, 2009 (Legalbox 44, Folder 1)
  - Agromeck, 2010 (Legalbox 44, Folder 2)
  - Agromeck, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Backup DVD, 2004-2005 (Cdbox 12)
    These files were originally received on a CD. The CD is not available for patron use. Copies of files from this CD are available upon request.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - General File, Including Applications for Editorship, 1943-1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - [Images] - Ag, 1998 (Cdbox 39)
  - Images for People Section: Seniors, Underclass, Baby Ads, 1999 (Cdbox 39)
  - [Images] - Last Scans, P-Z, 1999 (Cdbox 39)
  - Layout and Design Book, 1949 (Oversizeflatbox 43)
  - Notes - list of names, 1948 (Oversizeflatbox 43)
  - Photo CD 1, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 4, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 6, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 7, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 8, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 9, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 10, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 12 - Organizations, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 14 - Academics, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 15, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 16, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 17, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 18 - Student Life, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 20 - Sports, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photo CD 21 - Women's Tennis, Agromeck, Colleges, 2000 (Cdbox 39)
  - Production Disc 2/5, 1999 (Cdbox 39)
  - Production Files DVD Disk 2 of 3, 2007 (Cdbox 12)
    These files were originally received on a DVD. The DVD is not available for patron use. Copies of files from this DVD are available upon request.
  - Production Files DVD, 2007-2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD Disk 2, 2007-2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, cover - p.115, 2008-2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, p.176-277, 2008-2009 (Cdbox 2)
  - Production Files DVD, p.278-328, Web, Career Guide, 2008-2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, Disk 1 of 3, 2011 (Cdbox 39)
  - Production Files DVD, Disk 2 of 3, 2011 (Cdbox 39)
  - Production Files DVD, Disk 3 of 3, 2011 (Cdbox 39)
  - Publishing Contracts, 1940, 1963-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sales Ledger, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sales Tax Correspondence, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Yearbook Study Commission, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Damaged CDs and DVDs, 1998-2010 (Cdbox 47)
    These files were originally received on a CD. The CD is not available for patron use.
- Technician Records, 1939-2007; 1939 2007
  This series contains records from the Technician, the student newspaper at NCSU. It contains digital production files, staff applications, handbooks and manuals, budget and equipment information, cartoon work, letters to the editor, photographs, and contracts.
  - Applications for Editorship and Correspondence, 1939-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Associated Collegiate Press Newspaper Guidebooks, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Associated Collegiate Press Trip Summary, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cartoons- Drawings and Sketches, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cartoons- syndicated, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- Technician Reporters at Faculty Senate, March 1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and Budget Information, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Equipment Orders, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1978, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - National Newspaper Syndicate Subscriptions, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - News and Observer Article about editor Beverly Privette, 15 April 1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, January-June 2002 (Cdbox 39)
  - Photographs, July-December 2002 (Cdbox 39)
  - Print Shop Contracts, 1969-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Production Files DVD, 16-28 April 2008 (Cdbox 2)
  - Production Files DVD, April 2006 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, Summer 2006 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, August-September 2006 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, October 2006 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, November-December 2006 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, January 2007 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, February 2007 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, Summer 2007 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, August 2007 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, September 2007 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, November 2007 (Cdbox 39)
  - Production Files DVD, December 2007 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, January 2008 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, February 2008 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, March 2008 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, 1-15 April 2008 (Cdbox 3)
  - Production Files DVD, May-July 2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, August 2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, October 2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, November 2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, September 2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, December 2008 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, January 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, February 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, March 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 21 May 2009-30 July 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 19 August 2009-11 September 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 14 September 2009-16 October 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 19 October 2009-6 November 2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 9 November 2009-7 December 2009 (Cdbox 12)
    [photoarchives2]\preservation\UA016_035\Technician\DVD_Fall 2009 Technician Ty Johnson, editor 11-09-09 - 12-07-10_2009-2010
  - Production Files DVD, 12 January 2010-12 February 2010 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 5 April 2010-3 May 2010 (Cdbox 12)
  - Production Files DVD, 27 May 2010 - 27 Aug. 2010 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 30 Aug. 2010 - 22 Sept. 2010 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 23 Sept. - 19 Oct. 2010 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 20 Oct. 2010 - 11 Nov. 2010 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 12 Nov. 2010 - 6 Dec. 2010 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 10 Jan. 2011 - 14 Feb. 2011 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 15 Feb. 2011 - 28 Mar. 2011 (Cdbox 46)
  - Production Files DVD, 29 Mar. 2011 - 29 Apr. 2011 (Cdbox 46)
  - Staff Manual, 2006? (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Technician English Course, 1963-1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Technician Opinion Column, 8 February 1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Damaged CDs and DVDs, 2006-2010 (Cdbox 47)
- WKNC Student Radio Station Records, 1922-2006; 1922 2006
  This series contains records from WKNC, the student radio station at NCSU. It is arranged alphabetically and includes meeting minutes, technical notes, newsclippings, contracts, applications for the position of station manager, and photographs.
  - Collegiate Broadcasters Convention, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence and Applications for Station Manager, 1960-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Contracts, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General Station Records, 1949-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - General Station Records, 1952-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate Broadcasting System Handbook and Station Information, 1946-1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes and Report on WVWP Situation, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings, 1945-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings, 1965-1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina University Radio Network Coverage of the 1976 General Election (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Photocopies of Newsclippings and Articles, 1922?-1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1949-1972, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Raleigh Times Newsclippings, 30 September 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Station Manual, November 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Technical Notes and Sketches, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Technical Notes and Sketches, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Technical Notes, Wiring and Circuit Information, Equipment Inventories, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Training Manual, 2006? (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - WKNC Study Commission Meeting Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Windhover Records, 1928-2010; 1928 2010
  This series contains records from the Windhover, a literary magazine at NCSU. Included are staff applications, budget information, promotional flyers, digital production files, and publications. It is arranged alphabetically.
  - Budget Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Calls for Submissions and Senior Thesis on the Wataugan, 1928-1929?, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - General Records, 1964-1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Posters, 1990, 1993 (Flatfolder 1)
  - Production Files CD, 2010 (Cdbox 12)
  - Proposed Charter for Windhover, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Publication Contracts and Staff Applications, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Publicity and Calls for Submissions, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Staff Applications, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Windhover: an extensive collection of visual works, 1999 (Legalbox 44, Folder 3)
  - Windhover: art and literary production, 2001 (Legalbox 44, Folder 4)
  - Windhover, Spring 2009 (Legalbox 44, Folder 5)
    Some of these files were originally received on a CD. The CD is not available for patron use. Copies of files from this CD are available upon request.
  - Windhover, Spring 2010 (Legalbox 44, Folder 6)
  - Windhover, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Windhover (2 copies), 2006 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Other Student Publication Records, 1926-2010; 1926 2010
  This series contains records from smaller student media publications. Included is the Nubian Message, a newspaper representing the African American community at NCSU, and the Wataugan, a student literary magazine published in the first half of the twentieth century.
  - The Brick Production Files DVD, 2011 (Cdbox 46)
  - Nubian Message Production Files DVD, 2007-2008 (Cdbox 3)
  - Nubian Message Production Files DVD, 2008-2009 (Cdbox 12)
  - Pinetum Organization Information, 1967-1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Southern Engineer Records, 1963-1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - State Sentinel Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Student Publication of the School of Design Organization Information, 1968-1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Wataugan Records, 1926, 1949-1955 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Photographs, 1969-2010; 1969 2010
  The majority of the photographs in this series are from Student Media photographers at NCSU. Most were taken on campus and document special events, student organizations, extracurricular activities, campus buildings, and athletic competitions. Also included are a large number of photographs taken at the North Carolina State Fair. This series also contains promotional photographs released by NCSU News Services and a small amount of advertising material from private organizations.
  This series is arranged in three subseries: Photo CDs and DVDs, Photographic Prints, and Men's Basketball Photographic Prints. The first subseries is made up of digital images on photo CDs and DVDs, most of which date from the early 2000s. It is arranged alphabetically by subject. The second subseries dates mostly from the 1970s and 1980s and is also arranged alphabetically by subject. The third subseries is arranged chronologically, beginning with images from the 1970s and ending in the early 1990s.
  - Photo CDs and DVDs, 2002-2010; 2002 2010
    - [1998 Photo Archive] Disc 1736 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1998 Photo Archive] Disc 3161 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1998 Photo Archive] Disc 3190 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1998 Photo Archive] Disc 4027, 1999 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1998 Photo Archive] Disc 4028 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1998 Photo Archive] Disc 4029 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 0192 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 1550, 1998 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 3000 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 3977 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 3979 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 4307 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 4308 (Cdbox 39)
    - [1999 Photo Archive] Disc 4312 (Cdbox 39)
    - 2005-2006 Student Media Photographs - Disk 1 of 3, A-Gymnastics (Cdbox 12)
    - 2005-2006 Student Media Photographs - Disk 2 of 3, Football - Skateboarding (Cdbox 12)
    - 2005-2006 Student Media Photographs - Disk 3 of 3, Slip and Slide - Zupan (Cdbox 12)
    - 2006-2007 Photo Archive - Disc 1, A-B (Cdbox 2)
    - 2006-2007 Photo Archive - Disk 2, C-E (Cdbox 3)
    - 2006-2007 Photo Archive - Disk 3, F-K (Cdbox 3)
    - 2006-2007 Photo Archive - Disk 4, L-R (Cdbox 3)
    - 2006-2007 Photo Archive - Disk 5, S-U (Cdbox 3)
    - 2006-2007 Photo Archive - Disk 6, V-Z (Cdbox 3)
    - 2007-2008 Photo Archive, 3-C (Cdbox 3)
    - 2007-2008 Photo Archive, D-F (Cdbox 12)
    - 2007-2008 Photo Archive, G-L (Cdbox 12)
    - 2007-2008 Photo Archive, M-P (Cdbox 12)
    - 2007-2008 Photo Archive, R-S (Cdbox 12)
    - 2007-2008 Photo Archive, T-Z (Cdbox 12)
    - 2008-2009 Photo Archive - Disk 1, #-C (Cdbox 3)
    - 2008-2009 Photo Archive - Disk 2, D-F (Cdbox 3)
    - 2008-2009 Photo Archive - Disk 3, G-I (Cdbox 3)
    - 2008-2009 Photo Archive - Disk 4, J-O (Cdbox 3)
    - 2008-2009 Photo Archive - Disk 5, P-S (Cdbox 3)
    - 2008-2009 Photo Archive - Disc 6, S-Y (Cdbox 2)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 1, #-C (Cdbox 12)
    - 2009-2010 Photo Archive - Disk 2, D-F (Cdbox 12)